Inventory of the Norman Allderdice Collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Series II (Box 49)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions
    - "Our Own Kind," Rischin, Moses, 1960. (Folder 60: 4)
    - "The Political Animal," Hutchins, Robert M., 1962. (Folder 60: 5)
    - "The Power of Reason," Redfield, Robert, 1963?. (Folder 60: 6)
    - "Jobs, Machines, and People," Helstein, Ralph, and others, 1964. (Folder 60: 7)
    - "Dead Horse and the Featherbird," Jacobs, Paul, 1962. (Folder 60: 8)
    - "Labor Looks at Labor,", 1963. (Folder 60: 9)
    - "The Churches and the Public," Lekachman, Robert, and others, 1960. (Folder 60: 10)
    - "Science,", 1962. (Folder 60: 11)
    - "The Press,", 1961. (Folder 60: 12)
    - "Trial by Battle ...," Lamb, Edward, 1964. (Folder 60: 13)
    - "Toward Community ...," Lichtman, Robert, 1966. (Folder 60: 14)
    - "Religion,", 1962. (Folder 60: 15)
    - "The Police,", 1962. (Folder 60: 16)
    - "Religion and American Society,", 1961. (Folder 60: 17)
    - "The Government of Science," Stover, Carl F., 1962. (Folder 60: 18)
    - "The Rise and Fall of ..." Wheeler, Harvey, 1966. (Folder 60: 19)
    - "The Truth about the New ...," McBirnie, William S., undated. (Folder 60: 20)
    - "Medicine,", 1962. (Folder 60: 21)
    - "Permanent Peace and a World without War," Millis, Walter, 1961. (Folder 60: 22)
    - "U.S. Foreign ...," Neal, Fred Warner, 1961. (Folder 60: 23)
    - "Pacempeace ...,", undated. (Folder 60: 24)
    - "The Eichmann Trial ...," Rogat, Yosa, 1961. (Folder 60: 25)
    - "Birth Control ...," Stevas, Norman St. John, 1960. (Folder 60: 26)
    - "How the United States ...," Scheer, Robert, 1965. (Folder 60: 27)
    - "Stage and Screen,", 1962. (Folder 60: 28)
    - "Democracy and ...," Stieber, Jack, and others, 1960. (Folder 60: 29)
    - "The Government of Science," Stover, Carl F., 1962. (Box-folder 61: 1)
    - "Therefore Choose Life,", 1965.; See also box 59 (Folder 61: 2)
    - "To Live as ...," Tillich, Paul, and others, 1965. (Folder 61: 3)
    - "Keeping the World ...," Waskow, Arthur I., 1965. (Folder 61: 4)
  - "Center for United Labor Action," Copeland, Vincent, 1973. (Folder 61: 5)
  - Central Statistical Board of the GDR--"The GDR'S ...,", 1973. (Folder 61: 6)
  - Cereal Institute, Inc.--"FTC Proposals to Restrict ...,", 1998. (Folder 61: 7)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States
    - "Communists within ...,", 1947. (Folder 61: 8)
    - "The Economics of ...,", 1956. (Folder 61: 9)
    - "The Outlook for ...," Kirkpatrick, A. L., 1954. (Folder 61: 10)
    - Channing L. Bete Company--"Why Vote?", 1958. (Folder 61: 11)
      Scriptographic booklet
  - Chantico--"What Is Communism ...?" Schwarz, Fred, undated. (Folder 61: 12)
  - Charles E., Coughlin--"Persecution ...,", 1958. (Folder 61: 13)
  - Charles H. Kerr and Company
    - Fisher, Mark, "Evolution and Revolution,", undated. (Folder 61: 14)
    - Darrow, Clarence S., "The Open Shop," undated, booklet, and "Crime and Criminals," address, 1905. (Folder 61: 15)
    - Keracher, John
      - "Proletarian Lessons,", undated. (Folder 61: 16)
      - "Producers and Parasites,", undated. (Folder 61: 17)
    - Lafargue, Paul, "The Right to Be Lazy,", undated. (Folder 61: 18)
    - London, Jack, "The Strength of the Strong," 1911, and "The Apostate,", 1919. (Folder 61: 19)
    - Marcy, Mary, "How the Farmer ...,", 1916. (Folder 61: 20)
    - Marx, Karl, "Wage, Labor and Capital,", undated. (Folder 61: 21)
    - Marx, Karl, and Frederick Engels, "Communist Manifesto,", undated. (Folder 61: 22-23)
    - "Money ...," Landon, Melville D., 1895. (Folder 61: 24)
    - Marcy, Mary, "Industrial Autocracy,", 1919. (Folder 61: 25)
    - "Marxism and Darwinism," Pannekoek, Anton, 1912. (Folder 61: 26)
    - Simons, A. M.--"Class Struggles in America,", 1905. (Folder 61: 27)
    - "The Socialist Movement," Vail, Charles H., 1902. (Folder 61: 28)
  - Charles K. Pulse--"Questions and Answers,", undated. (Folder 61: 29)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons--"Are you an American?", 1944. (Box-folder 62: 1)
  - Chedney Press--"Wake Up America!" Josephson, Emanuel, 1959. (Folder 62: 2)
  - Chicago Council of American-Soviet Friendship--"Religion ...," Melish, William Howard, undated. (Folder 62: 3)
  - Chicago Pen and Hammer--"On Relief ...," Martin, Jack, undated. (Folder 62: 4)
  - Chicago Tribune Company--"The Civil Rights Bill,", 1964. (Folder 62: 5)
  - China Publishing Company--"Republic of China,", 1978. (Folder 62: 6)
  - China Reconstructs--"Medical Care ...,", 1978. (Folder 62: 7)
  - Chinese Information Services
    - "Maoism ...,", 1969. (Folder 62: 8)
    - "The Case of ...,", 1973. (Folder 62: 9)
    - "The Republic of China Today,", 1976. (Folder 62: 10)
  - Church Peace Mission--"A Positive ...," Gibson, George Miles, undated. (Folder 62: 11)
  - Christian and Missionary Alliance--Congo Tidings, 1933. (Folder 62: 12)
  - Christian Anti-Communist Crusade--Schwarz, Fred
    - "Insurance against Communism,", undated. (Folder 62: 13)
    - "The Heart, Mind ...,", 1952. (Folder 62: 14)
    - "Communism: Diagnosis and ...,", undated. (Folder 62: 15)
    - "Communist Interpretation ...,", undated. (Folder 62: 16)
    - "Christian Answer to Communism,", 1960. (Folder 62: 17)
  - Christian Beacon Press
    - McIntire, Carl
      - "The Testimony ...,", 1952. (Folder 62: 18)
      - "Bishop Oxnam ...,", 1953?. (Folder 62: 19)
    - LeRoy, William R., "Christianity without God or ...,", 1966. (Folder 62: 20)
  - Christian Citizen Press--"Precinct Premier,", 1962. (Folder 62: 21)
  - Christian Conservative Church--"Persecution ...," Stacey, David K., 1962. (Folder 62: 22)
  - Christian Crusade Publications
    - Hargis, Billy James
      - "Communism ...,", 1963. (Folder 62: 23)
      - "50 Counts of Treason ...,", undated. (Folder 62: 24-25)
      - "Communism and American Labor,", undated. (Folder 62: 26)
    - "Hearing before the Committee ...,", 1960. (Folder 62: 27)
    - "Little Known Facts ...,", undated. (Folder 62: 28)
    - "Death of Freedom of Speech ...,", 1967. (Folder 62: 29)
    - "Red Runs the Caribbean," Penabaz, Fernando, undated. (Folder 62: 30)
    - "Deviationists ...," Young, Glenn O., undated. (Folder 62: 31)
    - "Is the School House ...," Drake, Gordon V., undated. (Folder 62: 32)
    - "Communism ...," Noebel, David A., 1965. (Folder 62: 33)
    - "Is the School House the Proper Place to Teach ...,", 1968. (Folder 62: 34)
    - "The Beatles: A Study ...,", 1969. (Folder 62: 35)
    - "Siecus Corruptor of Youth,", 1969. (Folder 62: 36)
  - Christian Educational Association (Box 63)
    - "Frankfurter's Red Record," Crockett, Sam, 1961. (Folder 63: 1)
    - "Jewish Anti-Communism," Pickney, George, 1956. (Folder 63: 2)
  - Christian Freedom Foundation--Kershner, Howard E.
    - "Socialism: Reversal of God's Design,", undated. (Folder 63: 3)
    - "The Moral Basis of a Free Society,", undated. (Folder 63: 4)
    - "God, Gold and ...,", undated. (Folder 63: 5-6)
  - Christian Nationalist Crusade
    - "Abolish the United Nations,", undated. (Folder 63: 7)
    - "The Jews and their Lies," King, Martin Luther, 1948. (Folder 63: 8)
    - "Twenty Years of Treason ...," McCarthy, Joseph, undated. (Folder 63: 9)
      Manuscript
    - "Americans being Blackmailed?" Morgan, Roland L., undated. (Folder 63: 10)
    - "Mystery Manuscript,", 1965. (Folder 63: 11)
    - "Jews in ...," Smith, Gerald A., 1951. (Folder 63: 12)
    - "Mr. Smith ...," Smith, Gerald L. K., undated. (Folder 63: 13)
    - "Army General Exposes Jews," Moseley, George Van Horn, undated. (Folder 63: 14)
    - "Protocols of the Learned Elders of Zion," Marsden, Victor E., undated. (Folder 63: 15)
      Translation
    - Smith, Gerald L. K.
      - "Matters of Life and Death,", 1958. (Folder 63: 16)
      - "Too Much and Too Many Roosevelts,", 1950. (Folder 63: 17)
    - Tenney, Jack B.
      - "Mind-Washing in ...,", undated. (Folder 63: 18)
      - "Zion's Trojan Horse,", 1954. (Folder 63: 19)
    - "Jews on the ...,", undated. (Folder 63: 20)
    - "Jews Rule America ...," Smith, Gerald L. K., undated. (Folder 63: 21)
    - "Zionist Network," Tenney, Jack B., 1953. (Folder 63: 22)
    - "The Ultimate ...," Williams, Robert H., 1957. (Folder 63: 23)
  - Christian Resistance study project--"The Slanted, Slippery, Silent 'Press',", 1961. (Folder 63: 24)
  - The Christophers, Inc.
    - "George Washington Speaks for Himself,", undated. (Folder 63: 25)
    - "Uphold the Declaration of Independence,", undated. (Folder 63: 26)
      News notes
  - Chrysler Corporation
    - "Pattern for Strikes,", 1944. (Folder 63: 27)
    - "Beyond the Facts and the Records," comments on panel report to National War Labor Board, undated. (Folder 63: 28)
  - Church League of America--Eavey, C. Benton
    - "A Shocking Study ...,", undated. (Folder 63: 29)
      Review of a book
    - "Why the Methodist ...,", undated. (Folder 63: 30)
    - "The Sun and the Umbrella,", undated. (Folder 63: 31)
  - Church of the Brethren
    - "The Pacifist ...," Bittinger, Foster M., 1957. (Folder 63: 32)
      Course on peace
    - "The Noncombatant and ...,", 1955. (Folder 63: 33)
    - Peace packet, undated. (Folder 63: 34)
      Study materials
    - "Anti-Missile Missile," Schuhle, William, undated. (Folder 63: 35)
    - "Peace Studies," West, Dan, 1958. (Folder 63: 36)
  - Church Peace Mission
    - "The Christian Conscience ...,", 1953. (Folder 63: 37)
    - "Christian Faith ...," Scherer, Paul, undated. (Folder 63: 38)
  - Cinema Educational Guild, Inc. (Box 64)
    - Fagan, Myron C.
      - "Red Treason ...,", undated. (Folder 64: 1)
      - "Americans: A Blueprint ...,", 1955. (Folder 64: 2)
        News bulletin
      - "CFR Completely ...,", 1966. (Folder 64: 3)
      - "Can Ike Be our Salvation?", 1953. (Folder 64: 4)
      - "Civil Rights ...,", 1964. (Folder 64: 5)
      - "Communism by any other Name,", 1949. (Folder 64: 6)
      - "Crusade for Freedom ...,", 1950. (Folder 64: 7)
      - "Documentations of the Reds and Fellow Travelers ...,", 1951?. (Folder 64: 8)
      - "Documentations of the Red Stars ...,", 1950. (Folder 64: 9)
      - "Communism, Anti-Negroism ...,", 1964. (Folder 64: 10)
      - "Eisenhower ...,", 1951. (Folder 64: 11)
      - "The Eisenhower Myth,", 1955. (Folder 64: 12)
      - "Hollywood Backs UN ...,", 1953. (Folder 64: 13)
      - "How Hollywood Is Brainwashing ...,", 1964. (Folder 64: 14)
      - "How they Brainwash,", 1963. (Folder 64: 15)
      - "How TV Is Brainwashing the People,", 1964. (Folder 64: 16)
      - "The Kennedy Boys and our Invisible ...,", 1962. (Folder 64: 17)
      - "More about Brainwashing by an Expert ...,", 1964. (Folder 64: 18)
        News Bulletin
      - "Must We Have ...,", 1962. (Folder 64: 19)
      - "Naming the Traitors in the UN,", 1953. (Folder 64: 20)
      - "Only Impeachments Save ...,", 1960. (Folder 64: 21)
      - "Our Secret Government,", 1956. (Folder 64: 22)
      - "Patterns of Treason ...,", 1960. (Folder 64: 23)
      - "Our Invisible ...,", 1962-1965. (Folder 64: 24-25)
      - "Perhaps in view of Johnson's Voting ...,", 1965. (Folder 64: 26)
      - "Reds in the Anti-Defamation League,", 1950. (Folder 64: 27)
      - "Reds behind World Federalism,", 1949. (Folder 64: 28-29)
      - "Red Rainbow,", 1946. (Folder 64: 30-31)
        Play
      - "Red Stars ...,", 1964. (Folder 64: 32)
      - "Secret Minutes of ...,", 1954. (Folder 64: 33)
      - "The Strange Cases ...,", 1961. (Folder 64: 34)
      - "Thieves' Paradise,", 1946. (Folder 64: 35)
      - "Third Party to Save ...,", 1952. (Box-folder 65: 1)
      - "Treasonous ...,", 1963. (Folder 65: 2)
      - "The True Story of Yalta,", 1953. (Folder 65: 3)
      - "UNESCO: No. 1 Enemy of American Youth,", 1961. (Folder 65: 4)
      - "U.N. Is U.S. Cancer,", 1952. (Folder 65: 5)
      - "U.S. or U.N? Only One ...,", 1953. (Folder 65: 6)
      - "UWF Plot and ...,", 1962. (Folder 65: 7-8)
      - "Vox Populi: ...,", 1951. (Folder 65: 9)
      - "We Need the American ...,", 1952. (Folder 65: 10)
      - "We Now Have Our Own ...,", 1965. (Folder 65: 11)
      - "What Is this Thing Called: ...,", 1951. (Folder 65: 12)
      - "What We Must Do in 1956," (Folder 65: 13)
      - "What We Must Do Now,", 1964. (Folder 65: 14)
      - "Who Are the Real ...?", 1963. (Folder 65: 15)
      - "Why Ike Fears Bricker Amendment,", 1954. (Folder 65: 16)
      - "Why Kennedy Must Be Impeached,", 1962. (Folder 65: 17)
    - Fowler, George B.
      - "The Liberty Amendment,", 1963. (Folder 65: 18)
      - "A Geo-Political ...,", 1962. (Folder 65: 19)
    - Hancock, John, "Another Vital Report,", 1964. (Folder 65: 20)
    - Reinhardt, Bryson, "Treaties to Destroy America,", 1954. (Folder 65: 21)
  - CIO Postwar Planning Committee--"As We Win,", 1959. (Folder 65: 22)
  - Circuit Riders, Inc.--"Reorganize Red China?", 1958. (Folder 65: 23)
    Conference paper
  - Citizens Committee for a Free Cuba--Bethel, Paul D.
    - "Terror and Resistance ...,", 1964. (Folder 65: 24)
    - "Cuba and U.S. Policy,", 1966. (Folder 65: 25)
  - Citizens Committee to Preserve American Freedoms--"The Un-American Activities ...," Truman, Harry S., 1959. (Folder 65: 26)
  - The Citizens Council
    - "Integration Amendment ...," McGowan, M. M., 1962. (Folder 65: 27)
    - "A Jewish View on Segregation,", undated. (Folder 65: 28)
    - "A Christian View of Segregation," Gillespie, G. T., 1954. (Folder 65: 29)
    - "Racial Facts,", undated. (Folder 65: 30)
    - "Mixed Schools and Mixed Blood," Sass, Herbert Ravenel, undated. (Folder 65: 31)
    - "The Menace of Modern ...," Evans, H. W., 1923. (Folder 65: 32)
    - "The Truth Cries Out," Patterson, Robert B., 1966. (Folder 65: 33)
    - "What Is the Citizens Council Doing?", undated. (Folder 65: 34)
  - Citizens for Educational Freedom
    - "Inalienable Civil Rights ...," Daly, Anthony W., undated. (Folder 65: 35)
    - "D-Day for Federal School Aid?" Freeman, Roger A., 1960. (Folder 65: 36)
  - Citizens Foreign Aid Committee--"Foreign Aid and You,", 1959. (Folder 65: 37-38)
  - Citizen Information Center--"Survival" and "The Ten Fatal Delusions of Youth," Shofstall, W. P., undated. (Folder 65: 39)
  - Citizens for Reagan, undated. (Folder 65: 40)
  - Citizens Research Foundation--"Republican Campaign ...," Roady, Elston, and Carl D. McMurray, 1969. (Folder 65: 41)
  - Carroll, J. M., "The Trail of Blood,", 1931. (Folder 65: 42)
  - Clarendon Press--"Race in Europe," Huxley, Julian, 1939. (Folder 65: 43)
  - Clergymen's Committee on China--"Peace without Freedom?" Head, David C., undated. (Folder 65: 44)
  - Clinchy, Russell J., "Human Rights and the United Nations,", 1952. (Folder 65: 45)
  - Closer Ups--"The Anti-Defamation League ...," Williams. Robert H., 1947. (Folder 65: 46)
  - College of Chinese Studies, California College in China --"Reflections on the Basic Ideas of East and West," Flewelling, Ralph Tyler, 1935. (Folder 65: 47)
  - Collier's--"Revenge in Poland," Creel, George, 1943. (Folder 65: 48)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System--"What the New Radio Rules Mean,", 1941. (Folder 65: 49)
  - Columbia College Citizenship Council--"Columbia and the Community: ...," Rauch, Marc, and others, 1968. (Folder 65: 50)
  - "The Coming Generation in Europe," Johnson, James Wood, 1942. (Box-folder 66: 1)
  - Commission on Education--"Communism and the NAACP," Volume II, Matthews, J. B., 1958. (Folder 66: 2)
  - Commission on International Affairs--American Jewish Congress--"Hard Questions and Answers on the Middle East,", undated. (Folder 66: 3)
  - Committee for an Alert Methodism--"Do the Reds ...," Ryker, Kenneth W., undated. (Folder 66: 4)
  - Committee for Better American Relations in the Middle East--"Towards a Democratic State in Palestine ...,", 1970?. (Folder 66: 5)
  - Committee for Constitutional Government--"Survival," Fellers, Bonner, undated. (Folder 66: 6)
  - Committee for Industrial Organization--"The C.I.O.: What It Is and How It Came to Be,", 1937 (Folder 66: 7)
  - Common Council for American Unity--"The World We ...," Buck, Pearl S., and others, 1942. (Folder 66: 8)
    Addresses
  - Committee for Industrial Organization--"Labor and the Nation," Lewis, John L., 1937. (Folder 66: 9)
  - Committee for McCarthyism--"The Red-Addled Brain ...,", undated. (Folder 66: 10)
  - Committee for Maurice Sugar for Judge of Recorder's Court--"A Negro on Trial for his Life ...," Sugar, Maurice, 1935. (Folder 66: 11)
  - Committee for Negro-Jewish Relations--"The Jewish People and ...," Goldner, Sanford, 1953. (Folder 66: 12)
  - Committee for Monroe Doctrine--"The Monroe Doctrine ...," Clark, J. Reuben, 1928. (Folder 66: 13)
  - Committee for the Preservation of the Constitution--"What Is Metropolitan Government?", 1958. (Folder 66: 14)
  - Committee for the Preservation of Methodism--"Is there a Pink Fringe ...?", 1951. (Folder 66: 15)
  - Committee for the Re-election of the President--"The Clearest Choice,", 1973. (Folder 66: 16)
    Compilation of speeches
  - Committee for World Disarmament and World Development--"Security through World Disarmament,", 1961. (Folder 66: 17-18)
    Report of a conference
  - Committee of First Amendment Defendants--"Behind the Bars ...,", undated. (Folder 66: 19)
  - Committee of One Million--"Red China and the United Nations," Dominick, Peter H., undated. (Folder 66: 20)
  - Committee of the States--"Save the Republic," Olney, Robert C., 1967. (Folder 66: 21)
  - Committee on New Alternatives in the Middle East--"The Great Berrigan Debate,", 1974. (Folder 66: 22)
  - Committee on Pan-American Policy--"The Panama Canal ...," Tansill, Charles Callan, undated. (Folder 66: 23)
  - Committee on Postwar Tax Policy--"Financing Defense ...,", 1950. (Folder 66: 24)
  - Committee on Public Information--"The German-Bolshevik Conspiracy," Creel, George, undated. (Folder 66: 25)
  - Committee on State Sovereignty--"The Citizen in Politics,", 1958?. (Folder 66: 26)
  - Committee on Un-American Activities
    - "Communist Psychological Warfare (Brainwashing)," consultation with Edward Hunter, 1958. (Folder 66: 27)
    - "Kremlin's Espionage and Terror Organizations,", 1959. (Folder 66: 28)
      Testimony of Petr S. Deriabin
  - Committee to Defend Negro Leadership--"Ben Davis: Fighter for Freedom," Jones, Claudia, 1954. (Folder 66: 29)
  - Committee to Defend Alexander Trachtenberg--"Books on Trial ...,", 1952. (Folder 66: 30)
  - Commonwealth Club of California--"Liberalism versus Communism," Davies, A. Powell, 1947. (Folder 66: 31)
  - Communist Labor Party of America--"Program of the Communists," Bukharin, N., 1918. (Folder 66: 32)
  - Communist National Committee--"Manual for Community Club Leaders,", 1914. (Folder 66: 33)
  - Communist Party
    - "The Meaning of Socialism," Burns, Emile, 1950. (Folder 66: 34)
    - Death Penalty Demanded ...,", undated. (Folder 66: 35)
    - "For a Powerful United A. F. of L.,", 1936. (Folder 66: 36)
    - "Communism and Liberty," Gallacher, William, undated. (Folder 66: 37)
    - "The Struggle against White Chauvinism," Lawson, Elizabeth, 1949. (Folder 66: 38)
    - "Marxist Study Themes: Political Economy,", 1952. (Folder 66: 39)
      Reading material
  - Communist Party Election Committee (Chicago)--"Unite against Hunger,", 1935. (Folder 66: 40)
    Election platform
  - Communist Party Northern California District--Appendix to hearings before the Committee on Un-American Activities, 1960 (Folder 66: 41)
  - Communist Party of California--"Guide for Study and Discussion of William Z. Foster's Pamphlet: In Defense of the Communist Party,", 1949 (Folder 66: 42)
  - Communist Party of the People's Republic of China, Shah-chi, Liu, 1956. (Box-folder 67: 1)
    Political report
  - Communist Party--"Some ideological questions ...,", 1950. (Folder 67: 2)
    Material for classes and study groups
  - Communist Party, New York State
    - "Platform of struggle ...,", 1934. (Folder 67: 3)
      Election manifesto
    - "Constitution of the Communist Party ...,", 1945. (Folder 67: 4)
  - Communist Party of the U. S. A.--"The Advance of the United Front," Bittelman, Alex, 1934. (Folder 67: 5)
    Documentary account
  - Communist Party of the United States of America
    - Central Committee--"An Open Letter ...,", 1933. (Folder 67: 6)
    - "Caught! ...,", undated. (Folder 67: 7)
      Record relating to plagiarism
    - "Some Aspects of the ...," Jackson, James E., 1959. (Folder 67: 8)
    - "The MacArthur Ouster," Dennis, Eugene, 1951. (Folder 67: 9)
      Letter to the members
  - Communist Party of Southern California--"A municipal program for Los Angeles,", 1959. (Folder 67: 10)
  - Communist Party of the United States of America
    - "Communist Party and You," Gannett, Betty, 1946. (Folder 67: 11)
    - "McCarran Conspiracy ...,", 1951. (Folder 67: 12)
    - "On the Struggle against Revisionism,", 1946. (Folder 67: 13)
    - "Party Building,", 1943. (Folder 67: 14)
  - Communist Party--"Italy's New Path," Togliatti, Palmiro, 1945. (Folder 67: 15)
  - Communist Party of the United States of America
    - "The Practice of Bolshevik Self-Criticism ...," Tsirul, T., 1932. (Folder 67: 16)
    - "20th Anniversary of the Communist Party,", 1939. (Folder 67: 17)
  - Community lecture series--"The Three Great Commentaries of this ...," Oliver, Revilo, 1964. (Folder 67: 18)
  - Community Relations Service--"The People Take the Lead,", undated. (Folder 67: 19)
    Report of progress
  - Comparet, Bertrand L., "Israel's Fingerprints ...,", 1949. (Folder 67: 20)
  - Concordia Publishing House--"A Catholic President," Meyer, Carl S., 1960. (Folder 67: 21)
  - Conference on the Subject of Thought Control in the U.S.
    - No. 3, Literature, Music, the Arts ..., 1947. (Folder 67: 22)
      Proceedings
    - No. 4, Medicine, Science, and ..., 1947. (Folder 67: 23)
    - No. 5, The Film and the Actor, 1947. (Folder 67: 24)
    - No. 2, The Press, the Radio ..., 1947. (Folder 67: 25)
    - No. 6, Toward Freedom of Thought ..., 1947. (Folder 67: 26)
  - Congress of American-Soviet Friendship--"Tribute to Russia," Wallace, Henry A., 1942. (Folder 67: 27)
  - Congress of Freedom--"The Secret Government of the United States ...," Davison, Mary, undated. (Folder 67: 28)
    Open letters to United States senators
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations
    - "The CIO ...,", undated. (Folder 67: 29)
    - "Delegation to ...,", undated. (Folder 67: 30)
  - Congress of Racial Equality
    - "In Baton Rouge ...," Johns, Major, and Ronnie Moore, 1962. (Folder 67: 31)
    - "Sit Ins ...," Peck, Jim, 1960. (Folder 67: 32)
  - Connecticut League of Women Voters--"Freedom or Fascism?" Yale University Press, 1940. (Folder 67: 33)
  - Conservative Baptist Fellowship--"The Case against ...," Tulga, Chester E., 1948. (Folder 67: 34)
  - Conservative Society of America
    - "American Patriots Speak: Give me Liberty or Give me Death," Henry, Patrick, 1965. (Folder 67: 35)
    - "Support the Constitution ...,", 1961. (Folder 67: 36)
    - "Students for a Democratic Society ...," Courtney, Kent, 1969. (Folder 67: 37)
    - "Conservative Political Action Handbook," and "CSA Voting Index," Courtney, Kent and Phoebe, 1962. (Folder 67: 38)
    - "Labor's International Network," Berrier, Hilaire du, 1962. (Folder 67: 39)
  - Conservative Viewpoint Publishing Company--"Destroy the Accuser," Seelig, Fred, undated. (Box-folder 68: 1)
    Case history record
  - Constitutional Alliance
    - "Economic Depressions ...," Rothbard, Murray, 1969. (Folder 68: 2)
    - "No Substitute ...," MacArthur, Douglas, 1951. (Folder 68: 3)
    - "Inflation or Gold Standard?" Sennholz, Hans F., 1969. (Folder 68: 4)
    - "The Case for the Right to Work," Toledano, Ralph de, 1969. (Folder 68: 5)
  - Constitution Party U.S.A.--"To Restore and Preserve ...,", undated. (Folder 68: 6)
  - Constitutional Educational League